<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RebelCon</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on RebelCon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>#🙁😐🙂: Building a sentiment analyser for Twitter</title>
      <link>/talks/2019/donagh-horgan-building-sentiment-analyser-for-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2019/donagh-horgan-building-sentiment-analyser-for-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Can you teach a machine to understand emotion? It’s actually a lot easier than it sounds!
In this talk, I will show you how to iteratively build an AI-powered pipeline for Twitter sentiment analysis. A PhD in statistics is not required: we’ll start with a simple model and build towards more complex and powerful solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Quality Improvement with Business Outcomes</title>
      <link>/talks/2019/margaret-dineen-aligning-quality-improvement-with-business-outcomes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2019/margaret-dineen-aligning-quality-improvement-with-business-outcomes/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago I asked a question on Twitter &amp;ldquo;If you have a well thought out design, clean code, wonderful testing and painless deployment but the feature ends up never being used because the user didn’t want or need it in the first place, is that a quality feature?&amp;rdquo;
I got some very interesting responses.
We are very focused on how we deliver quality but maybe we need to spend more time looking at what we deliver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build and Deploy Rapidly with Serverless</title>
      <link>/talks/2019/christopher-paton-build-and-deploy-rapidly-with-serverless/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2019/christopher-paton-build-and-deploy-rapidly-with-serverless/</guid>
      <description>Serverless technology is relatively new and arguably began with the advent of AWS Lambda in 2015. Since then, serverless has become a hot buzzword which has been as greatly misunderstood as DevOps or container technology. This talk aims to demystify serverless concepts and illustrate the many benefits of embracing it. We will talk about common scenarios where serverless is beneficial and where it is not.
We will see a real-world demonstration application built on AWS technology (Lambda, API Gateway, DynamoDB, Elasticsearch, S3, CloudFormation and more) using .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CI/CD/CS - Continuous security in Kubernetes</title>
      <link>/talks/2019/jorge-salamero-continuous-security-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2019/jorge-salamero-continuous-security-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>Continuous Delivery helps to keep your software and Docker images updated and deploy new versions in production easily. Microservices are great reducing the attack vector and limiting the privileges or credentials access of each piece of your application. Containers provide an opportunity to implement better security, small, inmutable, single process and purpose. How can we implement a DevSecOps process?
In this session, we will discover real use case examples on how to make your CI/CD pipeline interact with Docker security tools and deploy Kubernetes security features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Testing in Agile</title>
      <link>/talks/2019/dan-ashby-continuous-testing-in-agile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2019/dan-ashby-continuous-testing-in-agile/</guid>
      <description>Software Testing is one of the most misunderstood things within the software industry. Too many people have misconceptions about the craft, but that’s probably because it&amp;rsquo;s hard to define and describe.
Lots of people look to models for answers, but because all models are fallible, they&amp;rsquo;ve added to the problem&amp;hellip; Take the automation pyramid as an example - Many people have formed testing strategies around the automation pyramid based on the flawed thinking that you can automate all the testing things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Culture eats improvement before breakfast</title>
      <link>/talks/2019/sabine-wojcieszak-culture-eats-improvement-before-breakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2019/sabine-wojcieszak-culture-eats-improvement-before-breakfast/</guid>
      <description>Breakfast is the meal where you prepare yourself for the day – for doing something great. In DevOps continuous improvement is an important goal for the individual, the team, the system and the organization. But what if the organizational culture is the way that improvement will be eaten before you can prepare for it?
This non-technical talk will tell the story of an ambitious project in difficulties and the half-hearted attempts to improve or even rescue it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Make Me Wait: Why Web Performance Is Critical for Product Success</title>
      <link>/talks/2019/paul-mcgrath-why-web-performance-is-critical-for-product-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2019/paul-mcgrath-why-web-performance-is-critical-for-product-success/</guid>
      <description>Web performance can make or break your product. Users now expect features to be fast, yet are constantly waiting for apps to download, bootstrap, or finish rendering.
Under-prioritising web performance, then, sets us up for early failure, unless we consider it as a guiding principle that we fold into both our design and development work-streams.
At Dell EMC, the Live Optics group have been building data analysis services since 2009. Recently we began to build the future foundations of our growing platform, led by this insight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friendly fire: how security software messes up</title>
      <link>/talks/2019/julie-matviyuk-friendly-fire-how-security-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2019/julie-matviyuk-friendly-fire-how-security-software/</guid>
      <description>How come, in the era of Deep Learning and advanced AI, security software does still mess up? Why is it so challenging to distinguish clean files from malware? How can you make sure your software won’t be blasted off customers’ machines?
I will present 10 simple things a software author can do to avoid it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From idea to sale in 6 months</title>
      <link>/talks/2019/kevin-duggan-from-idea-to-sale-in-6-months/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2019/kevin-duggan-from-idea-to-sale-in-6-months/</guid>
      <description>Chances are you have read a book with &amp;ldquo;Lean&amp;rdquo; somewhere in the title. These books are full of great ideas and advice. But how do you actually put them into practice? This talk details how, by adopting some of these lean principles, a fresh small team managed to turn a high-level business goal into a revenue delivering product in just six months.
Learn why you should talk less to your teammates and more to your customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Three Horse Race - Picking a Winner Between Coroutines, Reactive Streams and Effects</title>
      <link>/talks/2019/garth-gilmour-coroutines-reactive-streams-and-effects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2019/garth-gilmour-coroutines-reactive-streams-and-effects/</guid>
      <description>When developing scalable and responsive applications it is essential to leverage the parallelism provided by the underlying platform. Modern server hardware can support dozens, hundreds or even thousands of cores, but coding directly against these is beyond the reach of the vast majority of developers.
In modern JVM languages like Kotlin three approaches are available for simplifying the addition of parallelism. The first is the concept of Coroutines, which became an official and integral part of the Kotlin language in version 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mature microservices and how to operate them</title>
      <link>/talks/2019/sarah-wells-keynote/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2019/sarah-wells-keynote/</guid>
      <description>At the Financial Times, we built our first microservices in 2013. We like a microservices-based approach, because by breaking up the system into lots of independently deployable services - making releases small, quick and reversible - we can deliver more value, more quickly, to our customers and we can run hundreds of experiments a year.
However, to benefit from this new approach we had to make some pretty big changes to our culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence for Analysis of Medical Data from Newborn Infants</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/alison-oshea-ai-for-analysis-of-medical-data-from-newborn-infants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/alison-oshea-ai-for-analysis-of-medical-data-from-newborn-infants/</guid>
      <description>The volume of medical data being collected is continuously increasing as technology improves while the time and expertise required to analyse it is consistently scarce. Globally there is a critical shortage of radiologists to analyse scans and neurophysiologists to analyse EEG (brain-waves). At the INFANT research centre in University College Cork we are using artificial intelligence to develop tools which can analyse medical signals and scans to identify and quantify anomalies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building security into your workflow with InSpec </title>
      <link>/talks/2018/mandi-walls-building-security-into-your-worflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/mandi-walls-building-security-into-your-worflow/</guid>
      <description>InSpec is an open source testing framework for infrastructure with a human- and machine-readable language for specifying compliance, security, and policy requirements. Using a combination of command-line and remote-execution tools, InSpec can help you keep your infrastructure aligned with security and compliance guidelines on an ongoing basis, rather than waiting for and then remediating from arduous annual audits.
InSpec’s flexibility makes it a key tool choice for incorporating security into a complete continuous delivery workflow, reducing the risk of new features and releases breaking established host-based security guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuous delivery DevSecOps with Kubernetes: stay safe at the speed of light</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/david-gonzalez-continuous-delivery-devsecops-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/david-gonzalez-continuous-delivery-devsecops-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>Nowadays, Continuous Delivery is a must. Nobody starts a new application without asking: how can we make deployments as painless as possible? The only answer to it is Kubernetes. Full stop. Kubernetes is the solution to 99% of the problems on a software development/deployment pipeline because it was engineered for it.
The problem with CD pipelines is the security: there are no standards for securing a CD pipeline as it is something new and security takes time to catch up with the requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker: Our Journey to Production</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/david-mills-docker-journey-to-production/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/david-mills-docker-journey-to-production/</guid>
      <description>Xanadu Consultancy has provided software development and support for Matchbook.com, one of the worlds largest sports betting exchanges, for the past seven years. A sports betting exchange, like a financial exchange, is a highly transactional and low latency platform. Matchbook handles over 600M requests each day with an average response time of less than 2ms. The system is a distributed, micro services architecture. Xanadu operates a number of separate development teams delivering new features to Matchbook and supporting the production platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Failing by Succeeding</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/cate-huston-failing-by-succeeding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/cate-huston-failing-by-succeeding/</guid>
      <description>As individuals we - implicitly or explicitly - define success, as do teams. But how do these definitions and incentives impact how and what we build?
Let’s talk about the ways in which the dysfunctions of your organization become the dysfunctions of your product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frenemies: Strategies for UX and Product Management Alignment</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/tristan-ogorman-strategies-for-ux-and-pm-alignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/tristan-ogorman-strategies-for-ux-and-pm-alignment/</guid>
      <description>Product Management and UX ought to have shared goals, right? Both disciplines essentially seek to build software to help customers drive business outcomes. The reality is, however, that alignment between both roles is not always complete, especially in the white heat of agile development. This can happen for various reasons and this talk will identify the major problems that can cause misalignment and strategies for dealing with them as they arise or to help avoid them entirely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From tester to test coach, a voyage into the unknown</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/rob-meaney-from-tester-to-test-coach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/rob-meaney-from-tester-to-test-coach/</guid>
      <description>I believe that the evolving role of a tester is to advocate for and encourage the right testing to be done rather than performing the testing activity.
As a result of this belief I have embarked on a journey, from being a dedicated tester on a scrum team to a test coach advocating for quality and influencing test practices across an entire organisation.
In this session i&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the emotions, obstacles, successes and learning that I experienced during my journey so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Ventures Design Sprint</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/perera-design-sprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/perera-design-sprint/</guid>
      <description>How to Solve Big Problems and Test New Ideas in Just 5 Days?
How many meetings and discussions does it take before you can be sure you have the right solution? What’s the most important place to focus your effort, and how do you start? What will your idea look like in real life? Entrepreneurs and leaders face big questions every day. Now there’s a surefire way to answer these important questions; the SPRINT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helping communities &amp; products thrive by fostering empathy</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/sasha-romijn-helping-communities-and-products-thrive-by-fostering-empathy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/sasha-romijn-helping-communities-and-products-thrive-by-fostering-empathy/</guid>
      <description>Empathy is a fundamental part of human interaction. When we communicate by email or at conferences, or indirectly, when we create products, events, or do a talk. However, our understanding of other people is full of error, and worse, bias. This can lead us to make communities and products that work poorly for people that are different from ourselves, introduce confusion and misunderstanding, exclude people unintentionally, and sometimes even cause harm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to win at product analytics</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/noel-tate-how-to-win-at-product-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/noel-tate-how-to-win-at-product-analytics/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How to win at product analytics&amp;rdquo; gives easy to implement, practical tips on building an analytics culture within your company. This culture will give every team greater insight so everyone can ultimately build better products and offer a better service.
We’ll cover three areas:
 1: Setup and access 2: Sharing 3: Embedding analytics within existing processes  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving fast at scale</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/randy-shoup-moving-fast-at-scale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/randy-shoup-moving-fast-at-scale/</guid>
      <description>Most companies slow down as they get larger, but some actually get faster. This talk will discuss the speaker&amp;rsquo;s experiences leading high-performing engineering teams at Google, eBay, and Stitch Fix, and will discuss the organization, the processes, and the culture that can help a company move fast &amp;ndash; and even accelerate &amp;ndash; as it grows.
Modern software-service models take advantage of the great benefits in having the same team both build the software as well as operate it in production &amp;ndash; we call this DevOps, or simply &amp;ldquo;You Build It; You Run It&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Journey To Modular UI Development</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/david-lynam-journey-to-modular-ui/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/david-lynam-journey-to-modular-ui/</guid>
      <description>In recent years, microservice architecture has become an extremely popular way of delivering server side features. Microservices provide the ability to deploy isolated changes reducing the fear of undesirable side effects or bugs. Another benefit to this that they allow new teams to confidently make changes to code they fully understand. This has been observed numerous times in Poppulo where we’ve had many new starts deploy code to production within hours of starting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryanair&#39;s Agile Journey</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/jerry-osullivan-ryanair-agile-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/jerry-osullivan-ryanair-agile-journey/</guid>
      <description>Ryanair is a true Irish Success story and over the past 5 years it has made technology a central tenant in it’s future as it has grown it’s Ryanair Labs function to power the future of the airline. Hear how coordinating multiple teams in multiple locations is only possible with modern software engineering practices . The talk will give a sneak peek into Ryanair and Ryanair Labs. Learn how we deliver change at a rapid pace and how we are influencing the wider organisation to embrace agile as he make the journey to become the amazon of travel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Technology and Orgnizations Together</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/randy-shoup-scaling-technology-and-organizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/randy-shoup-scaling-technology-and-organizations/</guid>
      <description>Successful Internet companies are built on a foundation of excellent culture, efficient organization, and solid technology. As a company needs to scale, all of these parts of the foundation need to grow and scale with it. This tutorial will provide a deep dive into modern best practices at innovative companies in Silicon Valley for scaling culture, organization, and technology.
Driven primarily by the presenter&amp;rsquo;s experience ranging from small Valley startups to Google and eBay, we will learn about:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart buildings and smart cities</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/eric-thiebaut-george-smart-buildings-smart-cities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/eric-thiebaut-george-smart-buildings-smart-cities/</guid>
      <description>Is IoT a fad or is it the new tomorrow?
Smart buildings are connected buildings where distinct services such as badge scanners, temperature sensors, catering and other devices and services are all interconnected in order to enhance the value of the building, reduce cost, and offer a better working environment. Similarly, smart cities aim to fluidity traffic, reduce congestion, improve energy efficiency,… in order to provide a superior living environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting a startup within a startup</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/padraig-obrien-startup-in-a-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/padraig-obrien-startup-in-a-startup/</guid>
      <description>Starting a startup within a startup is a look back at Vectra.ai building their second product, a threat hunting tool called recall, what did it take to go from zero to our first customer, the difficulties when all your customers are enterprise customers. In my chat I will cover everything from:
 Getting your office setup Hiring people Trade-offs you will make when delivering software Getting going in a new domain, in this case, cyber-security Time-zone differences between offices in Ireland and the USA, silos and creating relationships with HQ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Board Whisperer</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/gary-fleming-the-board-whisperer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/gary-fleming-the-board-whisperer/</guid>
      <description>At this point in Agile’s lifecycle, many teams have switched to using a Kanban Board. Some are simple, three-column trackers; others are considerably more involved. Yet, many teams don’t know how to stop for a moment and listen to their board. It’s gently trying to nudge them about the changes that it needs to make them a better team. Come along and learn how we can go from simple to just complicated enough, smoothly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Build Trap</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/melissa-perri-build-trap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/melissa-perri-build-trap/</guid>
      <description>Are you building what your customers want, or are you just building?
Many companies confuse being busy with producing value, falling into a dangerous place called &amp;ldquo;The Build Trap&amp;rdquo;. They focus more on the motions of shipping feature after feature, without stopping to validate it’s what customer truly want and need. This is due in part to poor understanding of Product Management.
In order to get get out of the Build Trap and become a successful product-led organization, companies need to use strategy, process, principles, and practices to create an environment that focuses on outcomes for the user and the business rather than outputs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TypeScript Deep Dive</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/matija-grcic-typescript-deep-dive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/matija-grcic-typescript-deep-dive/</guid>
      <description>TypeScript is Microsoft’s answer to working large, complex JavaScript code-bases, bringing static typing and EcmaScript 6 features to current browsers. In this talk, you’ll learn how TypeScript was designed to extend and embrace JavaScript idioms and how it will help you out to ensure correct code and behavior.
We will also cover how to use advanced static types in practice by explaining how the compiler analyzes control flow to determine the most specific type for a variable at any given location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valuable Automation in Agile Testing</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/richard-bradshaw-valuable-automation-agile-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/richard-bradshaw-valuable-automation-agile-testing/</guid>
      <description>When talking about testing, hearing the word automation usually means automated tests, to some they are synonyms. But not to Richard Bradshaw. In his eyes Automation is integral to delivering software and even more so in delivering quality software. During this workshop, we’re going to discuss and explore ways we can use Automation to support our testing efforts far beyond automated checks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome failure! - Easier said than done!</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/sabine-wojcieszak-welcome-failure-easier-said-than-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/sabine-wojcieszak-welcome-failure-easier-said-than-done/</guid>
      <description>In the agile world we find a lot of slogans around the topic of failure: &amp;ldquo;Welcome failure&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;fail fast&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Fail early&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Fail often&amp;rdquo; are used regularly. And in theory we all agree that we can learn from failure. Some of us are also dreaming of a Blameless Culture.
But then daily business chatches us up&amp;hellip; The search for the guilty person starts as well as the finger pointing procedure! Everyone can breathe a sigh of relief not being identified as the originator of a failure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is This Cloud Native Thing Anyway?</title>
      <link>/talks/2018/sam-newman-cloud-native/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 18:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/2018/sam-newman-cloud-native/</guid>
      <description>Sam has found himself spending much of the past few years dealing with buzzword-heavy areas of technology, trying to come to terms with what it all means. From DevOps, to Microservices, serverless and now Cloud Native. So many of these terms mean different things to different people. In an effort to try and set us up with a common understanding of what Cloud Native is, Sam will be taking us on a whistle-stop tour through the history leading up to Cloud Native, and try and synthesise what it is, and why it’s important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/team/committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/committee/</guid>
      <description>test</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>